<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>Team Mimi Lee</title>
  <subtitle>Mimi Lee - the 45th Parliamentary Candidate for the People&#39;s Party of Canada in Kitchener-Conestoga. Join us in our mission to bring real change to Canada.</subtitle>
  <link href="https://teammimilee.ca"/>
  <link href="https://teammimilee.ca/feed.xml" rel="self"/>
  <updated>2025-04-06T00:00:00Z</updated>
  <id>https://teammimilee.ca</id>
  <author>
    <name>Mimi Lee</name>
    <email>teammimilee@teamppc.ca</email>
  </author>
    
    <entry>
      <title>Mimi Lee - From Far Left to Far Right (Part 1)</title>
      <link href="https://teammimilee.ca/2024/11/06/mimi-lee-from-far-left-to-far-right-part-1/"/>
      <updated>2024-11-06T00:00:00Z</updated>
      <id>https://teammimilee.ca/2024/11/06/mimi-lee-from-far-left-to-far-right-part-1/</id>
      <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Good day, everyone!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When I informed my friends and supporters that I would be the federal election candidate for the People’s Party of Canada (PPC), their reactions ranged from surprise to curiosity. My journey as a candidate for public office has been anything but conventional, and I’d like to share my story with you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You may know that I was once the Markham-Thornhill candidate for the Green Party of Canada (GPC). While my reasons for leaving the GPC are not the focus here, this is about my fresh start with the PPC.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;First and foremost, when COVID-19 descended on our country, I was deeply skeptical of the vaccine mandate. Eventually, I reluctantly received the first two standard vaccinations, as traveling was an absolute necessity for me. During my travels within Canada and abroad, I engaged in countless discussions about vaccinations—their consequences, the legality of mandates, and the medical evidence surrounding them. These conversations were as diverse as they were compelling, with strong opinions from colleagues and interest groups in Canada and Hong Kong. Each perspective deserved consideration.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, what prompted my shift to the PPC? Maxime Bernier stood out as the one party leader who unequivocally supported non-vaccinated citizens. Initially, my knowledge of the PPC was limited, but after researching their platform and having compelling discussions with committed and informed individuals, I decided to apply for candidacy. A phone call from Maxime Bernier himself sealed the deal. After a wonderful conversation, I chose to represent the PPC in the next federal election.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
    
    <entry>
      <title>Mimi Lee - From Far Left to Far Right (Part 2)</title>
      <link href="https://teammimilee.ca/2024/11/13/mimi-lee-from-far-left-to-far-right-part-2/"/>
      <updated>2024-11-13T00:00:00Z</updated>
      <id>https://teammimilee.ca/2024/11/13/mimi-lee-from-far-left-to-far-right-part-2/</id>
      <content type="html">&lt;br /&gt;
Welcome back! In my previous section, I shared my journey from the Green Party of Canada (GPC) to the People’s Party of Canada (PPC). Now, let’s explore why I chose the PPC and my stance on key issues.
&lt;h2&gt;Why PPC?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The PPC is the only party that consistently upholds Canadian values. As immigrants, many of us have chosen Canada as our home because of its uniqueness. We strive to integrate, contribute, and protect Canadian values while honoring our respective heritages. Back in summer 2019, I voiced on CBC’s Metro Morning that our country needs reform, and I stand by that belief.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Canada faces numerous challenges: neglected infrastructure, an outdated educational system, a housing crisis, an overwhelmed healthcare system, unsafe streets, and the consequences of nine years of governmental neglect. We must regroup, take stock, and rebuild. While welcoming immigrants is vital, we must drastically reduce that number and ensure Canada’s socio-economic and infrastructure systems before we can support more. Immigration policies should reflect not just numbers but compatibility with Canadian values, including respect for our flag, culture, and history.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Other key Issues&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Crime rate: The Canadian justice system is too lenient with repeated criminals, which should be addressed.&lt;br /&gt;
Internal Trade: It’s absurd that traveling within Canada is often more expensive than traveling abroad. Restrictions like limited alcohol transportation across provinces highlight a broken system. Mobility for skilled workers is restricted, stifling economic growth. Canadians deserve better.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Housing: Money laundering has distorted the housing market, making real estate unaffordable for genuine residents. We need better infrastructure, including bike lanes, to support overcrowded communities and encourage people to move to the outskirts.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Healthcare: Canada’s healthcare system has been inadequate for decades. A two-tier system, like the UK’s, could provide people with the choice to avoid long waits in the public system.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Foreign Policy: The UN has become dysfunctional, often siding with China and Russia. Canada should withdraw and develop political leverage and economic independence to protect human rights and natural resources.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Supply Management: Local food is often more expensive than imported food due to flawed supply management. This system needs reform.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Environment: Global warming is real, but it’s often exploited for hidden agendas. Practical solutions, like clean drinking water for remote First Nations communities, are essential.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Economy and Governance: The pandemic exposed Liberal-NDP mismanagement, worsening our economy. We need MPs who genuinely represent Canadians’ viewpoints, not party interests.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As we know, the big parties enforce a party whip, which means their MPs often prioritize the party’s stance over the voices of their constituents. If your MP isn’t listening to you, why are you voting for them? Smaller parties, on the other hand, are more likely to listen to voters because they’re working hard to earn your trust and your vote. Supporting these parties can lead to a more representative and responsive Parliament.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://nationalpost.com/opinion/rex-murphy-you-thought-lockdown-was-bad-just-wait-until-the-next-federal-election&quot;&gt;The late Max Murphy, one of the most influential commentators in Canada, wrote&lt;/a&gt; before the last election: “Candidates: This is the only area in which some small hope may be entertained. With well over 300 seats up for contest in the House of Commons, there will be at least three or four, in a good year even nine or 10, candidates who will prove upon election to be outstanding MPs, and even more, just outstanding citizens and people.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a board member of Fair Vote Canada for nearly 3 years (currently taking a Leave of Absence from the Fair Vote Canada Board while running my campaign), I believe it’s crucial to have more people represented in the House. Electoral reform allows us to push for a system that better reflects the will of the people and ensures every vote truly counts.&lt;br /&gt;
Please don’t hesitate to vote for candidates who have a passion to work for you (not for their parties) even though they might have certain stands that are different from you. You will never have complete consensus and no one will agree with any platform 100%, that’s life and that’s democracy. Agree to disagree and respect others’ opinions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you for reading. I hope this provides clarity on my stance and inspires you to engage in shaping Canada’s future.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
    
    <entry>
      <title>Financial Advisor and Advocate Announces Run for People&#39;s Party of Canada</title>
      <link href="https://teammimilee.ca/2025/04/06/financial-advisor-and-advocate-announces-run-for-peoples-party-of-canada/"/>
      <updated>2025-04-06T00:00:00Z</updated>
      <id>https://teammimilee.ca/2025/04/06/financial-advisor-and-advocate-announces-run-for-peoples-party-of-canada/</id>
      <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;(April 6, 2025, Markham, ON) – Mimi Lee, a former Green, has officially announced her candidacy for the People’s Party of Canada (PPC) in the upcoming federal election. Mimi, who previously ran in Markham-Thornhill also in 2021, brings a unique combination of expertise and dedication, making her a strong and diverse candidate.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With over 30 years of professional experience, Mimi has worked as a financial advisor for 20 years, her other experiences as an officiant, researcher, editor, reporter, publisher, and more, showcasing her adaptability and extensive skill set. She has also been an active blogger since 2000, witnessing the evolution of the internet. These experiences have equipped her with a deep understanding of societal changes and the ability to connect with people from all walks of life. In addition to her professional achievements, she has spent decades helping Canadian families embrace Canadian values, find meaningful employment, and build their futures.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mimi’s political journey began with her advocacy for human rights, particularly lobbying the Canadian government to support Hong Kong activists facing persecution under the Chinese Communist Party. In September 2020, she initiated Petition 2835, urging Canada to take stronger action against foreign interference activities. This effort led to the introduction of Motion M-55 in November 2020, which reaffirmed concerns about foreign interference and called for a robust government response. These initiatives culminated in the establishment of the Foreign Interference Commission in 2024, which held public hearings to examine the 2019 and 2021 elections. Later that year, in June 2024, Bill C-70 was passed, marking a significant step forward in addressing this critical issue.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“We have in Parliament right now, candidates and Members of Parliament are not loyal. Mimi is loyal to us, to our country and to Canadians. She is ready to fight for you.” Maxime Bernier, PPC leader stated, “Fighting for the real political refugees, people who believe in freedom, and are ready to fight for freedom, to be with us. So support Mimi, she is our candidate and she is ready to fight for you.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With a certification in human rights consultancy from the US Institute of Diplomacy and Human Rights (USIDHR), Mimi has consistently championed the importance of standing up for individual freedoms and ensuring that every voice is heard in Parliament.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Her decision to join the PPC stems from her dissatisfaction with the Liberal government’s handling of critical issues, particularly during the pandemic. Mimi has been vocal about the challenges faced by small businesses, criticizing the government’s policies that allowed large retailers to thrive while small shops struggled to survive. She believes that the PPC’s commitment to Canadian values and individual freedoms aligns with her vision for a better future.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mimi’s dedication to public service is evident in her track record. Despite being relatively new to politics, she has actively contributed to policy development, including drafting a proposal adopted by the Green Party in 2021. She has also served as a board member for Fair Vote Canada, advocating for electoral reform to ensure that every Canadian’s voice is represented in the House of Commons.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Her platform focuses on practical solutions to pressing issues such as deport overstays, ending corporate subsidies, housing affordability, healthcare reform, and infrastructure development. Mimi supports a two-tier healthcare system to address long-standing inefficiencies and believes in creating sustainable communities with better transit and infrastructure. She also emphasizes the need for a balanced immigration policy that ensures Canada’s socio-economic systems can support new arrivals while maintaining respect for Canadian values.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mimi is calling for a shift in governance, urging voters to elect MPs who prioritize their constituents’ needs over party agendas. She highlights the importance of independent voices in Parliament, stating, “We need representatives who truly listen to the people, not just follow party lines.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As the election approaches, Mimi hopes to inspire the citizens of Markham-Thornhill to vote for change and choose leadership that reflects their values and aspirations.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
</feed>