<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>Team Mimi Lee</title>
  <subtitle>Mimi Lee - the 45th Parliamentary Candidate for the People&#39;s Party of Canada in Kitchener-Conestoga. Join us in our mission to bring real change to Canada.</subtitle>
  <link href="https://teammimilee.ca"/>
  <link href="https://teammimilee.ca/feed.xml" rel="self"/>
  <updated>2025-03-22T00:00:00Z</updated>
  <id>https://teammimilee.ca</id>
  <author>
    <name>Mimi Lee</name>
    <email>teammimilee@teamppc.ca</email>
  </author>
    
    <entry>
      <title>Mimi Lee - From Far Left to Far Right (Part 1)</title>
      <link href="https://teammimilee.ca/2025/03/22/mimi-lee-from-far-left-to-far-right-part-1/"/>
      <updated>2025-03-22T00:00:00Z</updated>
      <id>https://teammimilee.ca/2025/03/22/mimi-lee-from-far-left-to-far-right-part-1/</id>
      <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Good day, everyone!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When I informed my friends and supporters that I would be the federal election candidate for the People’s Party of Canada (PPC), their reactions ranged from surprise to curiosity. My journey as a candidate for public office has been anything but conventional, and I’d like to share my story with you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You may know that I was once the Markham-Thornhill candidate for the Green Party of Canada (GPC). While my reasons for leaving the GPC are not the focus here, this is about my fresh start with the PPC.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;First and foremost, when COVID-19 descended on our country, I was deeply skeptical of the vaccine mandate. Eventually, I reluctantly received the first two standard vaccinations, as traveling was an absolute necessity for me. During my travels within Canada and abroad, I engaged in countless discussions about vaccinations—their consequences, the legality of mandates, and the medical evidence surrounding them. These conversations were as diverse as they were compelling, with strong opinions from colleagues and interest groups in Canada and Hong Kong. Each perspective deserved consideration.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, what prompted my shift to the PPC? Maxime Bernier stood out as the one party leader who unequivocally supported non-vaccinated citizens. Initially, my knowledge of the PPC was limited, but after researching their platform and having compelling discussions with committed and informed individuals, I decided to apply for candidacy. A phone call from Maxime Bernier himself sealed the deal. After a wonderful conversation, I chose to represent the PPC in the next federal election.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
</feed>